[{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679038784,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":4951,"timeElapsed":147467},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679040704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":84,"rt":1917,"timeElapsed":149387},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679042730,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":2025,"timeElapsed":151413},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679047439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4707,"timeElapsed":156122},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679053517,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":6077,"timeElapsed":162200},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679056394,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":2876,"timeElapsed":165077},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679058206,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1809,"timeElapsed":166889},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679061530,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3322,"timeElapsed":170213},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679063200,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"150","question":"Where are you from? Name all of the places you’ve lived.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1668,"timeElapsed":171883},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679073835,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":9831,"timeElapsed":182518},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679075211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1374,"timeElapsed":183894},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679076497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1284,"timeElapsed":185180},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679078267,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1768,"timeElapsed":186949},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679079369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":8,"rt":1100,"timeElapsed":188051},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679080623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":1253,"timeElapsed":189306},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679081961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":5,"rt":1336,"timeElapsed":190644},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679083150,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":3,"rt":1189,"timeElapsed":191833},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679085060,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1909,"timeElapsed":193743},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679088930,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":3032,"timeElapsed":197613},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679091211,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":2279,"timeElapsed":199894},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679094000,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2788,"timeElapsed":202683},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679096778,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":2777,"timeElapsed":205461},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679098653,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":23,"rt":1874,"timeElapsed":207336},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679099998,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1344,"timeElapsed":208681},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679101991,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1990,"timeElapsed":210674},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679103450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1458,"timeElapsed":212133},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679104642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1190,"timeElapsed":213325},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679105886,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"137","question":"How did you celebrate last Halloween?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1243,"timeElapsed":214569},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679110553,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3771,"timeElapsed":219235},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679111811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1256,"timeElapsed":220494},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679113500,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1688,"timeElapsed":222183},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679115283,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1783,"timeElapsed":223966},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679116384,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":1098,"timeElapsed":225067},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679117463,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":1079,"timeElapsed":226146},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679118473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1009,"timeElapsed":227156},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679120032,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":1558,"timeElapsed":228715},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679121166,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":1133,"timeElapsed":229849},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679126881,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":4056,"timeElapsed":235564},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679128445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1562,"timeElapsed":237127},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679130095,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":7,"rt":1649,"timeElapsed":238778},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679131539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":1443,"timeElapsed":240222},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679132847,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":11,"rt":1307,"timeElapsed":241530},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679134445,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":1597,"timeElapsed":243128},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679135790,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1344,"timeElapsed":244473},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679137078,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1287,"timeElapsed":245761},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679139897,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2819,"timeElapsed":248580},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679141453,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"67","question":"What role or responsibility did you have in your family that you later realized was not typical for your age?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1554,"timeElapsed":250136},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679149983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":7399,"timeElapsed":258665},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679151669,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1686,"timeElapsed":260352},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679154966,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":3296,"timeElapsed":263649},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679156247,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":1281,"timeElapsed":264930},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679157635,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1387,"timeElapsed":266318},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679158817,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1181,"timeElapsed":267500},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679160113,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1295,"timeElapsed":268796},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679161325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1209,"timeElapsed":270008},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679162377,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"115","question":"What would you do for a hobby and/or job if you had no restrictions of any kind?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1051,"timeElapsed":271060},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679166841,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":12,"rt":3489,"timeElapsed":275524},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679168122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1281,"timeElapsed":276805},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679169763,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1639,"timeElapsed":278446},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679172261,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":2498,"timeElapsed":280944},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679173367,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":19,"rt":1103,"timeElapsed":282050},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679174588,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":16,"rt":1220,"timeElapsed":283271},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679175623,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1033,"timeElapsed":284306},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679176908,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":10,"rt":1284,"timeElapsed":285591},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679178161,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"220","question":"If you had to live in a movie, book, or tv show universe (for example, the world of harry potter, twilight, dune or hunger games), which one would you choose and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":15,"rt":1252,"timeElapsed":286844},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679187050,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":7364,"timeElapsed":295733},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679188709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1656,"timeElapsed":297392},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679190142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":67,"rt":1433,"timeElapsed":298825},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679192551,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":2408,"timeElapsed":301234},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679193650,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1099,"timeElapsed":302333},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679221240,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":27588,"timeElapsed":329923},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679227269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":6028,"timeElapsed":335952},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679228678,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":1408,"timeElapsed":337361},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679230383,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"87","question":"If you could see or listen to one work of art as you die, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1703,"timeElapsed":339066},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679236225,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":4801,"timeElapsed":344907},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679238111,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":18,"rt":1885,"timeElapsed":346794},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679240039,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1928,"timeElapsed":348722},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679241452,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":1411,"timeElapsed":350135},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679242525,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":24,"rt":1074,"timeElapsed":351208},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679243919,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":13,"rt":1392,"timeElapsed":352602},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679245539,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":14,"rt":1619,"timeElapsed":354222},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679247003,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":17,"rt":1463,"timeElapsed":355685},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679248320,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"26","question":"If you were to become a close friend with somebody you had just met, please share something that would be important for them to know.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":28,"rt":1316,"timeElapsed":357003},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679253133,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":51,"rt":4013,"timeElapsed":361816},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679254527,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":1392,"timeElapsed":363210},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679255830,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":1301,"timeElapsed":364512},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679258496,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":2665,"timeElapsed":367179},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679259928,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":1432,"timeElapsed":368611},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679262144,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":2214,"timeElapsed":370826},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679263657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":1511,"timeElapsed":372340},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679265055,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1397,"timeElapsed":373738},{"subjectID":"23oj6a178a","prolificID":"614a8c315301f6c3b736a6d3","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b49f88a2d43f53bcc0f","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679266175,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"30","question":"If you were to die this evening with no opportunity to communicate with anyone, what would you most regret not having told someone? Why haven’t you told them yet?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":1120,"timeElapsed":374858}]